Patrick Ghidossi

970.227.1987 <u>patrick.ghidossi@gmail.com</u> github.com/patrickghidossi

Objective

A passionate, creative, and infinitely reliable problem-solver, Patrick believes in the web's ability to empower people and better their daily experience. He thrives in fast-paced, collaborative environments and is a skilled communicator who brings a diverse skillset to the table. His immediate goal is to develop, design, and test life-improving web applications.

Technologies

| -JavaScript | -jQu | ery -TypeSo | cript -Git | -HTML5 | |
|-------------|---------|-------------|------------|--------|--|
| -CSS3 | -NodeJS | -mongoDB | -Angular 2 | -React | |

Education

CodeCraft School of Technology, Boulder, Colorado

JavaScript-based Full Stack Web Development Academy

University of Colorado at Boulder, Boulder, Colorado

B.S. Media Studies, School of Journalism and Mass Communication Minor in History

Certificate in Applied Business

Summer Semester Abroad, the University of Arizona at the Centro Studi Città di Orvieto, Orvieto, Italy

Professional Experience

BuffStampede.com, Scout Network

Staff Writer 2015 - Present

Produce and plan multimedia web content before, during, and after CU football and basketball games.

Vail Resorts, Broomfield, CO

Accounts Payable: Senior Assistant, Card Services

2014 - 2016

Accounts Payable: Staff I Accountant

2013 - 2014

- Administered company AMEX and VISA programs.
- Managed critical vendor accounts. Generated and reviewed monthly accruals and journal entries.

Interests

- Contributor to the SB Nation site The Ralphie Report. Weekly analysis posts throughout football and basketball season.
- Patrick is an avid cyclist (Ride the Rockies 2013 & 2015, Triple Bypass 2013), an accomplished photographer, a
 passionate sports writer, and a fervent snowboarder.